https://bracha-lavee.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy policy
What information do we collect?
BRACHA-LAVEE.com does not require that you register.
We collect information from you when you register on our site.
When registering on our site, you may be asked to enter your: e-mail address.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To improve our website.To send periodic emails and special offers.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you submit your personal information.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, send an email notifying you of any changes, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us
our e-mail: Hello@bracha-lavee.com
HomeAboutOriginalsLinksFAQsGeneral Information
All images within this web site are protected under international copyright laws.Bracha Lavee Art studio. All rights reserved.
The copying, reproduction or distribution of these images by any means without the written approval of the artist Bracha Lavee is prohibited.
© 2020 Bracha Lavee art studio
privacy policy
terms of use
contact
